thewonderforest.com 2016-03-23

# Disclaimer / Privacy Policy – Wonder Forest

Everything you see on Wonder Forest was created by me unless otherwise stated. 

Wonder Forest contains some affiliate links. This means if you click on an affiliate link through to a retailer and purchase something, I may receive a very small amount or percentage of your purchase. This does not add any additional cost to you, the consumer. Adding affiliate links into a post occurs after a review/opinion on the product has already been formed.

This blog accepts paid advertising to help keep it running, as well as complimentary products for review. All complimentary products have been exclusively chosen by myself and will always be disclosed as “c/o” in the post. I never review products that I wouldn’t personally wear/buy/like and am not influenced by compensation. The views and opinions shared on this blog that have been written by me are entirely my own.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at dana@thewonderforest.com.

At www.thewonderforest.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thewonderforest.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.thewonderforest.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.thewonderforest.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.thewonderforest.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.thewonderforest.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Linkshare  
Amazon  
Glam Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.thewonderforest.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.thewonderforest.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thewonderforest.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

Some advertisements used on this blog are provided through Glam Media. I am not affiliated with any of the brands featured in the advertisements.

Wonder Forest uses cookies. By visiting this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. You can learn more about/disable cookies [here](http://www.southbourne.com/blog/2012/04/30/e-privacy-directive-websites).

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.
